- ConversationTopicId: 9401_Hint
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_Hint_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9401_Hint_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9402_Hint
  PlayerPrompt: "@9402_Hint_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9402_Hint_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9403_Hint
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_Hint_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9403_Hint_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9404_Hint
  PlayerPrompt: "@9404_Hint_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9404_Hint_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9405_Hint
  PlayerPrompt: "@9405_Hint_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9405_Hint_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9401_HorseTalk
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_FirstHorse_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9401_FirstHorse_start"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9405_LionTalk
  PlayerPrompt: "@9405_FirstLion_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9405_Kaluru_01_Dialogue"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9401_GoTo_Jochi_Topic
  PlayerPrompt: "@9401_Autopush_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9401_JochiKhan_02_Dialogue_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9402_GoTo_Francois_Topic
  PlayerPrompt: "@9402_Autopush_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9402_FranciosDeLaRama_02_Dialogue_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 9403_GoTo_Valencia_Topic
  PlayerPrompt: "@9403_Autopush_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@9403_ValenciaIznov_02_Dialogue"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
